Preliminary Guide to the Frank C. Brown Papers, 1899 - 1943 UA.29.02.0043
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject files, ca. 1924-ca. 1930
  - Hardware
    - Shovels (Box 21)
    - Stage (Box 21)
    - Telescopic Hoists (Box 21)
    - Wire (Box 21)
  - Harrell, M.P. [lye] (Box 21)
  - Harris-Dolian [mattresses and pillows] (Box 21)
  - Harrison, D.R. [floor cleaning] (Box 21)
  - Heating Control for the Various Buildings (Box 21)
  - Heating: Estimates and Contracts (Box 21)
  - Heating: Old Buildings and New (Box 21)
  - Heating Plant: Daily Records (Box 21)
  - Heating: Radiator Covers (Box 21)
  - Herald-Sun Papers (Box 21)
  - Herbarium Cases (Box 21)
  - Hester, J.H. [moving furniture] (Box 21)
  - Hibberd Florist (Box 21)
  - Higher Degrees- Other Institutions (Box 21)
  - Highways of North Carolina (Box 21)
  - Hobart Manufacturing Company [washing machines] (Box 21)
  - Hobgood and Broadwell [radiator service] (Box 21)
  - Hoists and Conveyors (Box 21)
  - Holcomb, J.I., Manufacturing Company [cleaning brushes and sanitary aids] (Box 21)
  - Holland Brothers [furniture- chairs] (Box 21)
  - Holloway, A.L. and Son [tires] (Box 21)
  - Home Insurance Agency (Box 21)
  - Hood Brick Company (Box 21)
  - Hopkins, Miss Emma B. [return receipt] (Box 21)
  - Hose (Box 21)
  - Hospital Consultants (Box 21)
  - Hospital and Medical School: Equipment (Box 21)
  - Hospital Lighting (Box 21)
  - Hospital Steel Cabinets (Box 21)
  - Hotel del Prado (Box 21)
  - Hotels (Box 21)
  - Hotel Gas and Storage Station (Box 21)
  - Houses and Property for Sale (Box 21)
  - Howard Dustless Duster Company (Box 21)
  - Hunt, S.R. [moving shrubbery] (Box 21)
  - Hymn Books (Box 21)
  - Ice Machines (Box 21)
  - Ideal Shade Company (Box 21)
  - Incinerators (Box 21)
  - Industrial Supply Corporation (Box 21)
  - Infirmary Equipment (Box 21)
  - Ink (Box 21)
  - Inquiries Concerning Our Plans, et cetera (Box 21)
  - Inquiries and Requests (Box 21)
  - Inquiries: Honor System (Box 21)
  - Insecticide (Box 21)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 21)
  - Institute of International Relations (Box 21)
  - Insurance Data (Box 21)
  - Insurance: Employers' Liability Policy and Endorsement (Box 21)
  - Insurance: Fire (Box 21)
  - Insurance: Life-- University (Box 21)
  - Insurance Liabilities (Box 21)
  - Insurance Analysis Reports (Box 21)
  - Insurance and Loans Companies (Box 21)
  - Insurance Policies and Bonds (Box 21)
  - Insurance on New Dormitories (Box 21)
  - Insurance Policies: Automobiles (Box 21)
  - Interior Decorations: Murphy Varnish Company (Box 21)
  - International Congress of Americanists (Box 21)
  - International Silver Company (Box 21)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 21)
  - Interstate Telephone and Telegraph Company (Box 21)
  - Iron and Copper: Toncan (Box 21)
  - Iron Specialties (Box 21)
  - Ivey, J.B., and Company [department stores] (Box 21)
  - Janitors' Supplies (Box 21)
  - Johnson and Faulkner [velvet] (Box 21)
  - Johnson Service Company [greenhouse] (Box 21)
  - Johnson Studio [photography] (Box 21)
  - Johns-Manville [packing sheets] (Box 21)
  - Jones and Frasier [watchmakers, manufacturing jewelers, china] (Box 21)
  - Jourdan Transfer Company [hauling furniture] (Box 21)
  - Jourdan, C.E. [brooms] (Box 21)
  - Journalism: American Association of Schools... (Box 21)
  - Junaluska Summer School (Box 21)
  - Kane, George W.-- Contractor [rock delivery] (Box 21)
  - Karagheusian, A.M., Incorporated [domestic floor coverings] (Box 21)
  - Kellogg Switchboard and Supply Company (Box 21)
  - Kemitex Products Company (Box 21)
  - Kueffel and Esser Company [drawing materials, mathematical (Box 21)
  - surveying instruments, measuring tapes] (Box 21)
  - Kewaunee Manufacturing Company [laboratory furniture] (Box 21)
  - Key Data: Abbreviations (Box 21)
  - Keys: Cabinets, Master Key Schedule, and Receipts and Other Data (Box 21)
  - King, H.C.-- Service Station (Box 21)
  - Kitchen and Hospital Equipment: Tidewater Sales Corporation (Box 21)
  - Kitchen and Store Equipment: Bishop and Babcock Sales Company (Box 21)
  - Kitchen Equipment (Box 22)
  - Klear Flax Linen Looms (Box 22)
  - Kleine, George W. [railway express] (Box 22)
  - Kleigl Brothers [lighting] (Box 22)
  - Kress [ash trays] (Box 22)
  - Kubar Manufacturing Company [asbestos, textiles, paints, and chemicals] (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Apparatus: Westinghouse (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Equipment (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Equipment: Welch Manufacturing Company (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Furniture and Equipment (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Furniture and Equipment: Data (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Furniture and Equipment: Kewaunee Manufacturing Company (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Supplies (Box 22)
  - Laboratory Tests (Box 22)
  - Lamps (Box 22)
  - Land (Box 22)
  - Land File (F.C.B.) (Box 22)
  - Lander, M.H. (drawing) (Box 22)
  - Landscape Architects (Box 22)
  - Landscape Plans: East Campus (Box 22)
  - Lang and Foot Carpets, Incorporated (Box 22)
  - Lantern Slides: Troy Studio (Box 22)
  - Lanterns: Japanese (Box 22)
  - Lathes and Arbors (Box 23)
  - Latta, E.J., Roofing Company (Box 23)
  - Laundry (Box 23)
  - Law Schedules (Box 23)
  - Lecturers (Box 23)
  - Lectures and Entertainment (Box 23)
  - Lettering and Letters: Bronze (Box 23)
  - Libraries: Prospective (Box 23)
  - Library Committee (Box 23)
  - Lifts (Box 23)
  - Liggett and Myers Tobacco Company (Box 23)
  - Lighting (Box 23)
  - Lightning Rods (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Hospital (Box 23)
  - Lindley Nurseries, Incorporated (Box 23)
  - Linoleum: Samples Of (Box 23)
  - Lipscomb-Gattis Company (gloves) (Box 23)
  - Lithoprinting: Edwards Company (Box 23)
  - Lloyd, A.E., and Company (hardware, paints, building materials) (Box 23)
  - Loaders, Portable (Box 23)
  - Lockers and Shelving: Steel-- Fred Medart Company (Box 23)
  - Long Distance Calls (Box 23)
  - Long, E.J.(painting and decorations) (Box 23)
  - Long, Orin (payment) (Box 23)
  - Love, John (opera seats) (Box 23)
  - Lumber: Memoranda (Box 23)
  - Lubrication and Filtration System (Box 23)
  - Lyon, W.C., Company (hardware, stoves, cutlery, glass, paints, oils, varnishes, lime, plaster, cement, harness, and saddlery) (Box 23)
  - MacBeth Daylighting Company (Box 23)
  - McDonald, D., and Company (gas meters) (Box 23)
  - McDonald Paint and Specialty Company (Box 23)
  - Macey Company (office supplies and furniture) (Box 23)
  - McGuire, F.J.(bricksand) (Box 23)
  - Machinery (Box 23)
  - Machines: Mailing, Stamping, Recording, Numbering, etc. (Box 24)
  - Mack International Motor Truck Corporation (Box 24)
  - Maftex: Insulation Board (Box 24)
  - Mailing Devices: Prices (Box 24)
  - Maintenance: Duke University (Box 24)
  - Manure (Box 24)
  - Manuscripts: Addresses, Articles (Box 24)
  - Manuscript Cases (Box 24)
  - Marble: Georgia (Box 24)
  - Markham and Jones Company (fertilizers, farm implements) (Box 24)
  - Martha Washington Tea Room (place cards) (Box 24)
  - Materials Taken by Whitted (Box 24)
  - Materials Used: Heating Plant (Box 24)
  - Materials Used (Box 24)
  - Mattreses and Pillows (Box 24)
  - May Day (Box 24)
  - May, D.C.(painting, papering and decorating) (Box 24)
  - Medals: Gold, Silver, and Bronze (Box 24)
  - Medals: Schwartz, Kirwin, and Fauss (Box 24)
  - Medart, Fred, Manufacturing Company (lockers and keys) (Box 24)
  - Medical Research (Box 24)
  - Medical School and Hospital (Box 24)
  - Meetings Outside of Durham (Box 24)
  - Memoranda of Furniture on Hand (Box 24)
  - Memorial Exercises in Memory of J.B. Duke (Box 24)
  - Memorials, Tablets, Stars, Windows (Box 24)
  - Merrymount Press: D.B. Updike (Box 24)
  - Metal: Magnolia Metal Company (Box 24)
  - Metal Coating (Box 24)
  - Metal Furniture: Bedroom (Box 24)
  - Metal Lath (Box 24)
  - Metal Lath Hangers:"Tie-To" Inserts (Box 24)
  - Metal Products: Erie Art Metal Company (Box 24)
  - Meters (Box 24)
  - Microscope and Projection Apparatus (Box 24)
  - Milk: Consignments (Box 24)
  - Mill: Power Supply Company (Box 24)
  - Millwork: Estimates (Box 24)
  - Mint, Edward W., Company (painting, decorating) (Box 24)
  - Minutes and Memoranda of Meetings at the Duke Endowment Office (Box 24)
  - Minutes: Building (Box 24)
  - Minutes: Committee on Business Administration of Expenditures (Box 24)
  - Mirrors: Furst Brothers and Company (Box 24)
  - Mitchell, A.S., Hardware Company (Box 24)
  - Mitchell Woodbury Company (china, pottery, glass, silverware, kitchen equipment, hotel supplies) (Box 24)
  - Models (of buildings) (Box 24)
  - Modern Electric Company (Box 24)
  - Modern Hospital Publishing Company (Box 24)
  - Morrison Manufacturing Company (bar, counter) (Box 24)
  - Morrow, R.B.(filing clerk, 9/26-1/2/27) (Box 24)
  - Moths: Recipes (Box 24)
  - Motion Picture Machinery: Burke and James (Box 24)
  - Motion Pictures: Bausch and Lomb (Box 24)
  - Motors: Gasoline (Box 24)
  - Mouldings (Box 24)
  - Moving Picture Booth (Box 24)
  - Moving Pictures and Apparatus (Box 24)
  - Moving Pictures and Apparatus (Box 25)
  - Multigraph Department (Box 25)
  - Murray, W.R., Company (piano covers) (Box 25)
  - Murrays, LTD: Booksellers (Box 25)
  - Museum: Philadelphia (Box 25)
  - Museum Cases (Box 25)
  - Museum Jars, etc. (Box 25)
  - Music: Choir (Box 25)
  - Napkin Rings (Box 25)
  - Nash, C.A. and Son, Incorporated (building material) (Box 25)
  - National Bureau of Education (Box 25)
  - National Products (Box 25)
  - National Theater Supply Company (Box 25)
  - National Youth Administration (Box 25)
  - Necessity Manufacturing Company (Box 25)
  - Neems, E.R. (chair repair) (Box 25)
  - Nelson, Thomas, and Sons (publishers and importers) (Box 25)
  - New England Sales Company (doorholders and doorstops) (Box 25)
  - Newport Manufacturing Company (moulding) (Box 25)
  - Newspaper Articles: Quarry (Box 25)
  - Ney, B. and Sons (office easy chairs: Sikes Company) (Box 25)
  - Noel Brothers Hardware Company (Box 25)
  - Noiseless Chairslide Company (Box 25)
  - North Carolina Bankers Association (Box 25)
  - North Carolina Bar Association (Box 25)
  - North Carolina College for Negroes
    - Architects (Box 25)
    - Bids and Estimates (Box 25)
    - Bids and Estimates (Box 25)
    - Bids and Estimates (Box 25)
    - Furniture and Fittings and Contracts (Box 25)
    - Design and furnishings (Box 25)
  - North Carolina Park Commission (Box 25)
  - Nosings [brass] (Box 25)
  - Numerals: Metal, Wood etc. (Box 25)
  - Nurseries (Box 25)
  - Nut Crackers (Box 25)
  - Odell Hardware (Box 25)
  - Office Assignments (Box 25)
  - Office Equipment: Tabulating (Box 25)
  - Offices: Memoranda and Agreements (Box 25)
  - Offices: Requests For (Box 25)
  - Official Communications from Deans, etc. (Box 25)
  - Oil Burners (Box 25)
  - Oil Filters: Burt Manufacturing Company (Box 25)
  - Oil: Heating (Box 25)
  - Oilers (Box 25)
  - Organization (Box 25)
  - Organs (musical) (Box 25)
  - Organs (musical) (Box 25)
  - Owl Pharmacy (Box 25)
  - Oxford Orphanage (Box 25)
  - Oxford Orphanage (Box 26)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 26)
  - Paint (Box 26)
  - Painters (Box 26)
  - Painting: Air Brush (Box 26)
  - Paintings, Portraits (Box 26)
  - Paper, Flags, Favors, Pencils, etc. (Box 26)
  - Parker-Gardner Company [furniture, carpets, draperies, victrolas, and victor records] (Box 26)
  - Partitions (Box 26)
  - Paschall Brothers [plumbing] (Box 26)
  - Payments (Box 26)
  - Payroll (1926-1927) (Box 26)
  - Peabody Drug Company (Box 26)
  - Pearl Cotton Mills (Box 26)
  - Pemberton, Mrs. Clarence [furniture hauling] (Box 26)
  - Pencils and Pencil Leads (Box 26)
  - Pencil Sharpeners (Box 26)
  - Pennsylvania Axminster Carpet Company (Box 26)
  - Persons Receiving Invitations to the Reception in 1926 (Box 26)
  - Persons Receiving Invitations to the Reception in 1927 (Box 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 26)
  - Phipps Hardware Company, Incorporated (Box 26)
  - Photographs (Box 26)
  - Physical Condition of Students (Box 26)
  - Physics Scoring (Box 26)
  - Pictures Sent to Mr. Gilbert (Box 26)
  - Pipe and Pipe Fittings (Box 26)
  - Pipe Hangers, etc. (Box 26)
  - Pipe Laying (Box 26)
  - Pipe (Box 26)
  - Plastic Ornaments (Box 26)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company (Box 26)
  - Plumbing (Box 26)
  - Plymouth Quarries (Box 26)
  - Pneumatic Tubes (Box 26)
  - Police Force: Durham (Box 26)
  - Police Officers (Box 26)
  - Pollard Brothers [hardware stores] (Box 26)
  - Pomona Terra Cotta Company (Box 27)
  - Pope Furniture Company (Box 27)
  - Post Office Boxes (Box 27)
  - Post Office Equipment (Box 27)
  - Postal Telegraph Company (Box 27)
  - Powe, E.K., Jr. [storm sewer] (Box 27)
  - Powell, Albert H., M.D. [treatmentof Mr. George Monnes] (Box 27)
  - Power Plant (Box 27)
  - Powers and Anderson Surgical Instrument Company (Box 27)
  - Preserving Lumber against Termites (Box 27)
  - Presidents (Box 27)
  - Press Clipping Bureaus (Box 27)
  - Pridgen and Jones [shoes-- rubber boots] (Box 27)
  - Princeton Quarries [rough natural building stone] (Box 27)
  - Printing [dies of seal, engravers, invitations] (Box 27)
  - Printing [samples of, mimeographing, engraving] (Box 27)
  - Prints (Box 27)
  - Public Hardware Company (Box 27)
  - Public Lectures Committee (Box 27)
  - Public Lectures: Receipts (Box 27)
  - Purchasing Department (Box 27)
  - Radiator Covers- Mullins Manufacturing Company (Box 27)
  - Radiator Covers- TriCo. (Box 27)
  - Radiators: H.B. Smith Company (Box 27)
  - Raleigh Granite Company [crushed granite] (Box 27)
  - Ramsey's Studio [photographic work] (Box 27)
  - Rand Kardex Corporation (Box 27)
  - Rand McNally and Company [printing and publishing] (Box 27)
  - Ranges: S.B. Sexton (Box 27)
  - Rawls Knight Company [cloth] (Box 27)
  - Receipts for express (Box 27)
  - Receipts for Insured Mail (Box 27)
  - Receipts for Reports: Work Done (Box 27)
  - Receipts for Stock (Box 27)
  - Receipts: Postal (Box 27)
  - Recorders (Box 27)
  - Reed and Barton [silversmiths, goldsmiths] (Box 27)
  - Refrigeration (Box 27)
  - Reports: Mr. Hall (Box 27)
  - Reports: Materials Received and Payroll (Box 27)
  - Reports on Progress of Erection of Buildings (Box 28)
  - Requisitions (Box 28)
  - Review of Reviews, Incorporated [sets of O. Henry] (Box 28)
  - Rieder, W.A. [furniture- display cases] (Box 28)
  - Riggs, Distler, and Company [mechanical and electrical construction] (Box 28)
  - Riley, S.O. [court costs] (Box 28)
  - Road Building (Box 28)
  - Roads and Road Covering- Tarvia (Box 28)
  - Rochelle, S.E. [bicycles, motorcycles, radios, guns, locks, general repairs, and keys] (Box 28)
  - Rochelle, Z.E. [crushed stone] (Box 28)
  - Rogers Drug Company (Box 29)
  - Roofing (Box 29)
  - Rope: Wire- A. Lescher and Sons Rope Company (Box 29)
  - Rose Agency [office outfitters/ pencils] (Box 29)
  - Rosner Sales Agency, Incorporated [linens] (Box 29)
  - Ross, F.H., and Company, Incorporated [robes, napkins, table linens] (Box 29)
  - Rowe, Marcellus [manure] (Box 29)
  - Royall and Borden [furniture and rugs] (Box 29)
  - Russel and Erwin Manufacturing Company [New Britain, Connecticut] (Box 29)
  - Safes: Mosler Safe Company (Box 29)
  - Sargent and Company [New Haven, Connecticut] (Box 29)
  - Sash Cords: Silver Lake Company (Box 29)
  - Scalecide [Insecticide] (Box 29)
  - Scarborough and Hargett [funeral services for Mrs. Josh Hopson] (Box 29)
  - Schoettle, Edwin J., Company [paper boxes and mailing tubes] (Box 29)
  - School of Religion: Rental of Gowns (Box 29)
  - Scientific and Cinema Supply Company (Box 29)
  - Scientific Apparatus: Physics (Box 29)
  - Scott, E.T., Company [furniture and supplies for barbers and beauty parlors] (Box 29)
  - Screens and Casement Windows (Box 29)
  - Sears, I.L. [tobacco] (Box 29)
  - Seeds: T.W. Woods and Sons (Box 29)
  - Seeman, E.A. [book- "History of Durham"] (Box 29)
  - Seeman Printery (Box 29)
  - Separk Foundry (Box 29)
  - Sewer Cleaning Equipment (Box 29)
  - Shades (Box 29)
  - Sharpe and Coleman Company [explosives] (Box 29)
  - Shaw, R.J. [manure] (Box 29)
  - Shearer, W.O., Motor Company (Box 29)
  - Shearman Concrete Pipe Company (Box 29)
  - Shelving, Steel (Box 29)
  - Shinn, T.S. [payroll account] (Box 29)
  - Shovels (Box 29)
  - Shower Mixers: Powers Regulator Company (Box 29)
  - Shrubbery (Box 29)
  - Signs and Culverts: Beiger Manufacturing Company (Box 29)
  - Silver Cleaners: American Laundry Machinery Company (Box 29)
  - Silver Specialties: Manhattan Emblem Company (Box 29)
  - Simmons Company [dormitory beds] (Box 29)
  - Skylights (Box 29)
  - Smith- Albright Company [millenery] (Box 29)
  - Smith- Courtney Company [supplies and machinery] (Box 29)
  - Smith, James A. and Son [plastering contractors] (Box 29)
  - Snider- Fletcher Company Lenses (Box 29)
  - Soda Fountains (Box 29)
  - Soda Fountain Tables (Box 29)
  - Soot Blower: Bayer Company (Box 29)
  - Sorrell Hardware Company, Incorporated (Box 29)
  - South-Eastern Underwriters Association (Box 29)
  - Southern Desk Company (Box 29)
  - Southern Power Company (Box 29)
  - Southern Spring Bed Company (Box 29)
  - Southgate, J. and Son (Box 29)
  - Southgate Memorial Hall (Box 29)
  - Spalding Brothers [tennis courts and equipment] (Box 29)
  - Specialties (Box 29)
  - Speed, Dr. J.A. [professional services] (Box 29)
  - Stadiums [separated to Wallace Wade Stadium folder] (Box 29)
  - Stage Lighting (Box 29)
  - Stage Lighting (Box 29)
  - Stairs and Safety Treads: Guarsteel (Box 29)
  - Stamps and signs: Matthews, James H. (Box 29)
  - Standard Oil Company (New Jersey) (Box 29)
  - Stanfield, William [payment for labor] (Box 29)
  - Stationary, Index Cards, etc.: Samples of (Box 29)
  - Stechert, G.E. and Company [books and periodicals] (Box 29)
  - Steel: Sheet Steel Trade Extension Committee (Box 29)
  - Steel Racks and Lockers (Box 29)
  - Steel Shelving: Art Metal Construction Company (Box 29)
  - Steene, William [payment for cleaning and varnishing paintings] (Box 29)
  - Stevens and Brown [American library and literary agents] (Box 29)
  - Stewart, John A. [telegram- commencement speakers] (Box 29)
  - Stewart, W.M. [sewer rods] (Box 29)
  - Still, J.T. [city building inspector] (Box 29)
  - Stock (Box 29)
  - Stokers- Mill Power Supply Company (Box 29)
  - Store Fronts: The Kawneer Company (Box 29)
  - Strassel, J.L., Company [furniture] (Box 29)
  - Strudwick, Dr. M.C. [professional service rendered Alex McNeil] (Box 29)
  - Subveyors: Samuel Olson and Company (Box 29)
  - Surfacing: Roads and Tennis Courts- Kylock (Box 29)
  - Surveying (Box 29)
  - Swift and Company [Sunbrite cleaner] (Box 29)
  - Switchboard Instruments (Box 29)
  - Tate Products [mop and cordage company] (Box 29)
  - Taylor and Phipps [hardware stores] (Box 29)
  - Teer, Nello L. [grading contractor] (Box 29)
  - Telephone Automatic Systems (Box 29)
  - Telephone Equipment (Box 29)
  - Tennis Courts- Concrete (Box 29)
  - Terra-Cotta (Box 29)
  - Testing Machines: "Riehle" (Box 29)
  - Thermometers (Box 29)
  - Thermostatic Control (Box 29)
  - Thermostatic Control (Box 30)
  - Thomas and Howard Company [wholesale grocers] (Box 30)
  - Thomas, Arthur H., Company [laboratory apparatus and reagents] (Box 30)
  - Thomas, George P. [rubber agent] (Box 30)
  - Thomas Quickel Company [ink, brushes, etc.] (Box 30)
  - Tile [art and flooring] (Box 30)
  - Tomlinson Company Incorporated [plumbing and heating supplies] (Box 30)
  - Tools Record (Box 30)
  - Toomey, T.C. [payroll account] (Box 30)
  - Torsch and Franz Badge Company [buttons] (Box 30)
  - Tractors: Kearney and Trecker Corporation (Box 30)
  - Tree Planting: American Tree Association (Box 30)
  - Trinity College Book Room (Box 30)
  - Tomlinson Chair Manufacturing Company (Box 30)
  - Trucks (Box 30)
  - Tyree, W.A. [key distribution] (Box 30)
  - Underwood, N. [builder] (Box 30)
  - Underwriters' Salvage Company (Box 30)
  - Union Electric Contracting Company (Box 30)
  - United States Military Academy (Box 30)
  - University of California (Box 30)
  - University of Michigan (Box 30)
  - Valiant, J.G. and Company (Box 30)
  - Valves,Gauges, etc.: Smith-Courtney Company (Box 30)
  - Van Arsdale- Harris Lumber Company (Box 30)
  - Van Scriber, J.B. (Box 30)
  - Vault Ventilators: McClintoch Company (Box 30)
  - Ventilation (Box 30)
  - Virginia-Carolina Chemical Company (Box 30)
  - Vitex Manufacturing Company [automatic extension stools and automative equipment] (Box 30)
  - Vonnegut Hardware Company (Box 30)
  - Waddey, Everett, Company [engraved invitations] (Box 30)
  - Wallace and Tierman Company, Incorporated [water and sewage purification] (Box 30)
  - Washington Duke Hotel (Box 30)
  - Water, Water Department (Box 30)
  - Water Proofing Material (Box 30)
  - Watson, George E., Company [paint] (Box 30)
  - Watts Hospital (Box 30)
  - Weed and Grass Killer (Box 30)
  - Weeks, Lem: Settlement of Sales (Box 30)
  - Welamb Company: Foreman's Daily Report (Box 30)
  - Westbrook, J.H., Jr. [commencement robes] (Box 30)
  - West Main Filling Station (Box 30)
  - Western Electric Company, Incorporated (Box 30)
  - Western Union (Box 30)
  - Whitaker Paper Company (Box 30)
  - White Furniture Company (Box 30)
  - Williamson, C.A. [Princeton quarries] (Box 30)
  - Wind Indicator: Lord Electrical (Box 30)
  - Windows and Casements: American Window Company (Box 30)
  - Window Devices (Box 30)
  - Window Lighting (Box 30)
  - Winston-Salem Chair Company (Box 30)
  - Wire: Rome Wire Company (Box 30)
  - Wood, George T. [confirming sale of rug] (Box 30)
  - Woolworth, F.W., Company [oilcloth] (Box 30)
  - Worth Motor Company (Box 30)
  - Wrenn Brothers Company [furniture] (Box 30)
  - Wright Company, The [hotel, restaurant, cafeteria, college, and institution equipment] (Box 30)
  - Wynne, Miss Elizabeth [clerical services] (Box 30)
  - Yearbook: Swift and Company (Box 30)
  - Collection plates, Duke Chapel, 1934 (Box 30)
- Oversize Materials, 1 box
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31)